soonersetc.com 2014-06-26

# Sooners Etc - Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

Sooners Etc believes that electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. We know you're concerned about protecting your privacy online. At Sooners Etc, we treat your personal information with the highest standards of safety, security, and confidentiality.

## Information Gathered

We don't collect personal information without your knowledge. We don't sell, rent, or give your personal information to unrelated third parties period.

This policy explains what information we collect about you and how we use that information. We also outline the choices you have.

## Cookies

Sooners Etc does not require the use of cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Sooners Etc cannot and does not control these cookies.

**Information concerning the Google DoubleClick DART cookie:**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Sooners Etc.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Sooners Etc's users based on your visit to Sooners Etc and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Traffic Data

Each time a visitor comes to the Sooners Etc site, information is collected to improve the overall quality of the Sooners Etc site. Sooners Etc collects the visitor's domain name/IP Address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from netscape.com or yale.edu or 255.255.255.0), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to the Sooners Etc site), and browser/platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Macintosh platform).

Sooners Etc also counts, tracks, and aggregates the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flow at Sooners Etc (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from and how traffic flows within the sites). Sooners Etc may merge this information into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners. Sooners Etc will not disclose your individual identity or personal data. When Sooners Etc does present aggregated information to potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

## Sharing and Usage Of Information

Sooners Etc never shares, sells, or rents any personal information unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information.

Further information pertaining to privacy and legal issues can be viewed [here](http://www.securityfocus.com/columnists/450).
